wis.dm 2008-12-16

# wis.dm

Effective as of 24th April 2008 

### Introduction 

Welcome to wis.dm, a vibrant social scene bursting with people, passion and promise that enables members to explore, experiment and discover other attitudes towards life and meet people they don’t know, but should (the “wis.dm Service”). We understand you may not want everyone in the world to have access to the information you share on wis.dm, which is why we believe you should have control over your personal information, in terms of both the nature and extent of the information you supply, as well as with whom you are prepared to share that information. By using or accessing wis.dm, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Information collected by wis.dm 

There are several types of information that are provided to us: 

  * personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us; 
  * information and content that you upload and contribute; and 
  * information collected by us as you interact with wis.dm 

When you register to become a member of wis.dm, you submit certain personal information, such as your name and email address and any other personal or preference information that you choose to submit. We also collect your browser type and IP address. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies”. Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login information on a user's system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve the quality of our service and make it easier to use. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do so. When you use wis.dm, there is a variety of functionality at your disposal. We collect information on your use of such functionality so that we can provide you with the wis.dm Service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain such information. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. If you post personally identifiable information in areas of the site accessible to other users, you should be aware that such information can be read, collected, or used by other users of these areas, and could be used improperly to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums or for others’ misuse of such information. Any misuse or improper collection of information provided on wis.dm is a violation of the wis.dm Terms of Use and should be reported. wis.dm may also collect information about you from other sources, such as blogs and other users of the wis.dm Service through the operation of the service (e.g. topic tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. By using wis.dm, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States. 

### Age Limitation 

Anyone under the age of fourteen (14) is not eligible to use the wis.dm Service and must not submit any personal information to us. 

### Use of Information 

When you register with wis.dm, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to other users in accordance with your privacy settings to enable you to connect with other users of wis.dm. We may use your name and email address to contact you from time to time and we will use your email address for security purposes to confirm that you are who you say you are. You can control the types and frequencies of certain emails you receive. Profile information is used by wis.dm primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information based on your privacy settings. In some cases where your privacy settings permit it, other wis.dm users may be able to supplement your profile. wis.dm may use information in your profile, such as items you view, without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating and analyzing data and site usage, and to customize the site’s content, layout and services as well as personalizing advertisements, promotions, products and services. We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to blogs and other users of the wis.dm Service, to supplement your profile. Where such information is used, we generally allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your profile. 

### Sharing Information with Third Parties 

We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is necessary. We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer, such as using a third party to host the wis.dm Service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about wis.dm, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the wis.dm-specified purposes. We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the wis.dm Service or using the wis.dm name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through on-site offers. We may offer stores or provide services jointly with other companies on wis.dm., and we may share customer information with that company in connection with your use of that store or service. If the ownership of all or substantially all of the wis.dm business, or individual business units owned by Soflow, Inc., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. Advertisements that appear on wis.dm are sometimes delivered directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. wis.dm does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on wis.dm unless you choose to share it with them. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by wis.dm and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers. 

### Links 

wis.dm may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by wis.dm. 

### Internet Awareness 

Whenever you voluntarily post personal information in public areas you should be aware that this information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by others to send you unsolicited communications. Please exercise discretion in deciding what information you disclose. 

### Changing and/or Removing Information 

You can review and revise your personal information, and who will be given access to your personal information, at any time. You have the option to cancel your membership at any time by sending an email to feedback@wis.dm. 

### Security 

The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account password. Please do not disclose your account password to unauthorized people. wis.dm uses industry standard technology designed to help keep your personal information safe. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us. 

### Changes in Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or delete portions of this Privacy Policy at any time without further notice. If we do this, we will post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this page and will indicate at the top of this page the Privacy Policy's effective date. Your continued use of the wis.dm Service after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to regularly review this Privacy Policy. 

### Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at feedback@wis.dm.
